thatweddingwebsite.com.au 2012-03-28

# Privacy Policy - That Wedding Website

Your online privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we provide a link to it on every page of our website.

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices of the www.ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au website and also applies to each of the other sites withinThatWeddingWebsite.com.au.

ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au provides links to many other websites that are beyond our control. Websites that we link to may have privacy and security policies that differ from ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au. Please understand that we are not responsible, in any manner, for the privacy, security practices, or content of such websites. 

**Privacy Notice Table of Contents:**

1)  The Information We Collect & How We Use It

2)  With Whom Does AllWedding.com Share Information

3)  Notification of Changes To The Privacy Policy

4)  Choice / Opt-Out Of Promotional and Marketing Communications

5)  Our Commitment to Data Security

6)  How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

7)  How To Contact Us

  * **1)** **The Types of Information We Collect And How We Use It:**

IP Addresses  
We use IP Addresses for statistical and system administration purposes. IP addresses are anonymously logged to track a user’s session. We do not link IP addresses with any personally identifiable information. This means that a user’s session will be logged but that user will remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP address to identify a user when necessary to enforce our terms of service or protect our site, network, advertisers or users.

Cookies  
ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au uses session cookies to prevent banner network and affiliate system abuse and cheating. This cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information about users. ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au does not require a user to accept or use browser cookies. Most web browsers will allow you the option to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept.

Contact Information  
We collect contact information (like your name, address, telephone number, email address and URL) through various registration forms, surveys, sweepstakes entry forms. 

This information is used to provide you with services that you requested (like submitting your website to our search engine, joining our link exchange service, or if you order products and services), contact you when necessary, or to send you additional information regarding ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au or selected reputable partners and affiliates.

Demographic Information  
We may occasionally collect demographic information (like your wedding date, level of education etc).  We use this information to learn more about the users and visitors of our website as well as to tailor our site to provide a positive experience for our users.

Unique Identifying Information  
We require users of certain services (like our search engine, link exchange, web hosting, and email services) to select or use unique usernames and passwords for use with those services.  We use this information for security purposes and to prevent unauthorised use, access, alteration or misuse of your accounts and services.

Financial Information  
We collect financial information (like credit card and/or banking information) from users who order goods, products or services from us.  We will use this information to bill and collect for the goods, products and/or services that you order. We will also use this information to confirm your registration qualifications where appropriate.

**2)** **With Whom Does ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au Share Information:**

ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone, except as expressly described below:

1)We have your express consent to share your information

2)We need to share your information to provide you the product or service that you requested. Only you can initiate this sharing by choosing to fill-out one of our online order forms (which are clearly labelled)

3)We believe in good faith that any applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it.

4)When the disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user.

We may share generic, aggregate and anonymous information with advertisers and affiliates 

ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au does not control the practices of our advertisers. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to their content, please contact them directly. (ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au will divulge information only as necessary to comply with state and federal laws.) 

**3)** **Notification of Changes To The Privacy Policy:**

Our privacy policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

If at some point in the future, ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au changes the usage practices that effect any of your personally identifiable information, We will notify you by email of the changes. At the time of that message you will be able to opt-out of this information usage by submitting a request to 

[support@thatweddingwebsite.com.au](mailto:support@thatweddingwebsite.com.au).

**4)** **Choice / Opt-Out Of Promotional and Marketing Communications:**

If you no longer wish to receive our occasional newsletters or other marketing communications from ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au you may opt-out of receiving these by following the unsubscribe / removal instructions located at the very bottom of these communications or submit a request to  [support@thatweddingwebsite.com.au](mailto:support@thatweddingwebsite.com.au).

Several of our services require registered participants to receive system announcements, invoices or other official communications from ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au. Users of these services must receive these important notifications as a condition of service.  
 ****

**5)** **Our Commitment To Data Security:**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate administrative procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  If you have any questions about the security at ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au please submit a query to  [support@thatweddingwebsite.com.au](mailto:support@thatweddingwebsite.com.au)

**6)** **How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect by editing your account information directly.  To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making changes or corrections to any of your personally identifiable information.  
 ****

**7)** **How To Contact Us:**

If you have any questions about the ThatWeddingWebsite.com.au privacy commitment, the practices of this site, or your dealings with us please submit a query to  [support@thatweddingwebsite.com.au](mailto:support@thatweddingwebsite.com.au)
